lol-pix.com 2014-11-30

# LOL Pix funny pics

We respect your privacy... we really do :)

This Privacy Policy is covering all applications we own and operate ("us" "we" or "our") such as fail.me.

This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any information you submit to us through our applications. This includes "Personal Information," which is information about you that is personally identifiable such as your name, e-mail address, user ID number, and other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing, as well as "Anonymous Information," which is information that is not associated with or linked to your Personal Information and does not permit the identification of individual persons.

User Consent

By accessing or otherwise using our application, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy you expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information and Anonymous Information according to this Privacy Policy.Your Personal Information may be processed by us in the country where it was collected as well as other countries (including the United States) where laws regarding processing of Personal Information may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

Collection and Use of Information

Personal Information

In general, we collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily through our apps. We also collect information that you submit in the process of creating or editing your account and user profile on our application as email address, etc. When you personalize your profile and use the features of our application, we will collect any information you voluntarily provide, and we may also request optional information to support your use of our application, such as your year of birth, gender and other demographic information. We collect information in the form of the content that you submit during your use of our, such as photos, reviews, ratings, voted options and other information you choose to submit. We may also collect information about you and your friends who use our application, from any social network you may have connected from, in order to provide you with a more personalized experience. For instance, we may collect your user ID or profile information that you have permitted to be displayed through our application in order to display you as a friend or in association with your profile and collections. When you order our products or services, you will need to submit your PayPal information or other payment information so that our service providers can process your payment for those products and services. When you sign up for, or win, any contests, or other activities that we make available on our application, we will collect the information designated along with such activity, which may include your contact information such as your address and phone number. If you choose to sign up to receive information about products or services that may be of interest to you, we will collect your email address and all related information. Additionally, we collect any information that you voluntarily enter, including Personal Information, into any postings, comments, or forums within the application community.

fail.me application addendum

Via fail.me application we are collecting users’ data such: Basic information - set by Facebook by default - name, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, and any other information you have shared with everyone.

Personal Information from Other Sources

We may receive Personal Information about you from other sources with which you have registered, companies who we have partnered with (collectively, "Partners") or other third parties. We may associate this information with the other Personal Information we have collected about you.

E-mail and E-mail Addresses

If you send an e-mail to us, we will collect your e-mail address and the full content of your e-mail, including attached files, and other information you provide. We may use and display your full name and email address when you send an email notification to a friend through our application or the social network from which you have connected to our application (such as in an invitation, or when sharing your content). Additionally, we use your email address to contact you on behalf of your friends (such as when someone sends you a personal message) or notifications from a social network or other website with whom you have registered to receive such notifications. We may use this e-mail address to contact you, for things such as notifications of limited edition shop sales, application features' updates and other related information. You may indicate your preference to stop receiving further promotional communications as further detailed below.

Information Collected Via Technology

As you use our application, certain information may also be passively collected and stored on our or our service providers’ server logs, including your Internet protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use Cookies and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URL) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed, or on which of the advertisements displayed on our application you clicked. This type of information is collected to make our application and solutions more useful to you and to tailor the experience with our application to meet your special interests and needs.

We may also enable advertisers and ad servers to promote third-party products and/or services by placing advertisements on our application. These advertisers and ad servers may use Cookies and/or "Web Beacons" (which are usually small, transparent graphic images) in order to monitor information related to served advertisements. Clicking on such advertisements will direct you to the website of a third-party and the advertiser. This Privacy Policy does not cover the privacy practices of any advertisers or ad servers.

Use and Disclosure of Information

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not generally sell, trade, rent, or share the Personal Information that we collect with third parties, unless you ask or authorize us to do so.

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used by us to provide you access to our application, to improve it, to better tailor the features, performance, and support of our application and to offer you additional information, opportunities, promotions and functionality from us, our partners or our advertisers at your request. Additionally, we do share your content preferences and other information with the social network from which you have connected to our application, along with those companies and persons you have asked us to share your information with.

We may provide your Personal Information to third-party service providers who work on behalf of or with us to provide some of the services and features of our application and to help us communicate with you. Examples of such services include sending email, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing payments (including credit card payments), and providing customer service. We require our third-party service providers to promise not to use such information except as necessary to provide the relevant services to us. We may share some or all of your Personal Information with our third-party partners, those with whom we have a co-branding or promotional relationship, or other third-parties about whom you are otherwise notified and do not request to opt out of such sharing. This Privacy Policy does not cover the use of your personally identifiable information by such third-parties. We do not maintain responsibility for the manner in which third parties, including, without limitation, social networks, other partners and advertisers, use or further disclose Personal Information collected from you in accordance with this Privacy Policy, after we have disclosed such information to those third parties. If you do not want us to use or disclose Personal Information collected about you in the manners identified in this Privacy Policy, you may not use our application.

Additionally, we may create Anonymous Information records from Personal Information by excluding information (such as your name) that would otherwise make the Anonymous Information personally identifiable to you. Generally, we aggregate this information and use it in statistical analysis to help us analyze patterns in the use of our application. This Privacy Policy does not limit our use or disclosure of any Anonymous Information in any way, and we reserve the right to use and disclose Anonymous Information to our partners, advertisers and other third parties in our discretion.

Although we currently do not have a parent company, any subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under a common control, we may in the future, and we may share some or all of your Personal Information with these companies, in which case we will require them to honor this Privacy Policy.

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your Personal Information may be among the assets transferred. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur and are permitted by this Privacy Policy, and that any acquirer of ours or that acquirer’s assets may continue to process your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on us; or (b) to protect and defend our rights or property, you, or third parties. You hereby consent to us sharing your Personal Information under the circumstances described herein. Also, we may disclose your Personal Information as Facebook Identification Number, voted options and/or demographic data as gender, age, etc. to the Third parties to help them to contact you as a winner of the contest you joined and the Third Party created using our application.

THE ABILITY OF OTHERS TO VIEW YOUR INFORMATION

Helping you to protect your information is a vital part of our mission. It is up to you to make sure you are comfortable with the information you choose to provide us and the information you choose to publish. You understand that when you use our application, certain information you post or provide through it, such as your name, profile, comments, collections and reviews, may be shared with other users and posted on publicly available portions of our application, including without limitation, chat rooms, bulletin and message boards, along with other public forums. Please keep in mind that if you choose to disclose Personal Information when posting comments or other information or content through our application, this information may become publicly available and may be collected and used by others, including people outside our community. We will not have any obligations with respect to any information that you post to parts of our application available to others, and recommend that you use caution when giving out personal information to others in public forums online or otherwise. We also share the information you publish with other third parties.

Using Your information and/or personal assets by Third party we are not responsible for any use or display of your personal information or personal assets as your name, picture, etc. by any Third party as other Social Network users, etc. We will not do any steps towards these users or their post unless the posts are racist, offensive or contain sexual abuses.

Third Party Sites and Advertising

Our application may contain links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such other websites. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of each and every website they visit. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through our application and does not apply to these third-party websites. The ability to access information of third-parties from our application, or links to other websites or locations, is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such third-parties, their products, their services, other websites, locations or their content.

Your CHOICES REGARDING YOUR Personal Information

We offer you choices regarding the collection, use, and sharing of your Personal Information. When you receive promotional communications from us, you may indicate a preference to stop receiving further promotional communications from us and you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the promotional e-mail you receive or by contacting us directly (please see contact information below).

Despite your indicated email preferences, we may send you administrative emails regarding our application, including, for example, administrative confirmations, and notices of updates to our Privacy Policy if we choose to provide such notices to you in this manner.

fail.me application addendum

If you wish us to remove all your data from our database please contact us via the Contact form and provide us with the link to your Facebook profile page.

Feedback

If you provide feedback to us, we may use and disclose such feedback for any purpose, provided we do not associate such feedback with your Personal Information. We will collect any information contained in such feedback and will treat the Personal Information in it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You agree that any such comments and any email we receive becomes our property. We may use feedback for marketing purposes or to add to or modify our services without paying any royalties or other compensation to you.

Security

We are committed to protecting the security of your Personal Information. We use a variety of industry-standard security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. Even though we have taken significant steps to protect your Personal Information, no company, including us, can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

Contact and Revisions

If you have questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us at via Contact form.

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision at our discretion.
